publicwhitepages.com 2016-06-18

# Public Profiles - Privacy Policy

﻿   

> Privacy Policy   Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.publicwhitepages.com and profilogical and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to profilogical include www.publicwhitepages.com, profilogical, www.profilogical.com and www.yourpublicprofile.com. The profilogical website is a a data management company site. By using the profilogical website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.   Collection of your Personal Information profilogical may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. profilogical may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and religion. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.   Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by profilogical. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the profilogical website.   profilogical encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from profilogical so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. profilogical is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the profilogical website.   Use of your Personal Information profilogical collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.   profilogical may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from profilogical and its affiliates. profilogical may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.   profilogical does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.   profilogical may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to profilogical, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.   profilogical will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on profilogical or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of profilogical; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of profilogical, or the public.   Security of your Personal Information     profilogical secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.   Children Under Thirteen profilogical does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.   Opt-Out & Unsubscribe We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from profilogical by contacting us here: \- Web page: profilogical \- Email: profilogical.com@gmail.com \- Phone: N/A   Changes to this Statement profilogical will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. profilogical encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how profilogical is protecting your information.   Contact Information profilogical welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that profilogical has not adhered to this Statement, please contact profilogical at:   profilogical 364 burr oak blvd po box 274 nelsonville, Ohio 45764   Email Address: uspninternet@gmail.com   Telephone number: 740-447-1707   Effective as of May 12, 2016  

﻿
